♪ So hang your stockings
and say your prayers ♪
(radio turns off)
♪ 'Cause Santa Claus
is coming tonight... ♪
(Bernadette(singing):)Why'd you turn it off?
(Sheldon:)Because in the last ten minutes,
Santa came to town,
(Sheldon:)kissed Mommy and ran Grandma
over with a reindeer.
(Sheldon:)I had a drunk uncle
who did all those things.
(Sheldon:)Nobody sings songs about him.
(Bernadette:)Maybe you'd like it more if you
thought of Santa as a superhero
(Bernadette:)and his power is bringing joy
to children.
(Sheldon:)My uncle was accused
of that, too.
(Sheldon:)It turned out
to be legal in Oklahoma.
(Bernadette:)Okay, new subject.
(Bernadette:)Let's talk
about presents.
(Bernadette:)What did you get Amy?
(Sheldon:)Oh, we're not exchanging gifts.
(Bernadette:)Come on, Sheldon, you
have to get her something.
(Sheldon:)Why should I?
(Sheldon:)She knows
that I don't like Christmas,
(Sheldon:)and yet, every year,
she forces me to celebrate it.
(Sheldon:)Not only am I going to this
foolish dinner against my will.
(Sheldon:)At the Christmas tree lot,
there was mistletoe,
(Sheldon:)and she kissed me
under it in public.
(Sheldon:)Like we were the stars
of a Tijuana sex show.